<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<Export generator="Cache" version="24">
<Class name="Cosmic.MetaTag.ClassType">
<Description><![CDATA[
<pre>
Copyright (c) 2011 Alex Woodhead

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy of this software
and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal in the Software without restriction,
including without limitation the rights to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense,
and/or sell copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is furnished to do so,
subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT
NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT.
IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY,
WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE
SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.
</pre>]]></Description>
<Super>%Library.String</Super>
<TimeCreated>62310,71027.34399</TimeCreated>

<Parameter name="DISPLAYLIST">
<Description><![CDATA[
Used for enumerated (multiple-choice) attributes.
Used in conjunction with the <a href="#VALUELIST">VALUELIST</a> parameter for enumerated
(multiple-choice) attributes. <var>DISPLAYLIST</var>, if not null,
represents the display values for the attribute corresponding with
the logical values listed in <var>VALUELIST</var>.
<p>The display values are returned by the <a href="#LogicalToDisplay">LogicalToDisplay</a> method.]]></Description>
<Default>,ClassDefinition,CompiledClass</Default>
</Parameter>

<Parameter name="COLLATION">
<Description>
The default collation value used for this data type.</Description>
<Default>EXACT</Default>
</Parameter>

<Parameter name="VALUELIST">
<Description><![CDATA[
Used for enumerated (multiple-choice) attributes.
<var>VALUELIST</var> is either a null string ("") or a delimiter
separated list (where the delimiter is the first character) of logical values.
If a non-null value is present, then the attribute is restricted to values
in the list, and the validation code simply checks to see if the value is in the list.]]></Description>
<Default>,cd,cc</Default>
</Parameter>
</Class>
</Export>
